Glorious 39 is a war, drama, history film directed by Stephen Poliakoff.
A mysterious tale set around a traditional British
family on the eve of World War Two.
Oblivious to the looming shadow of World War II, the wealthy Keyes maintain a confident
façade in the British countryside until daughter Anne becomes an unexpected pawn.
Her accidental discovery of secret recordings creates a rift in the family.
Anne Keyes, played by Romola Garai.
Alexander Keyes, played by Bill Nighy.
Aunt Elizabeth, played by Julie Christie.
Ralph Keyes, played by Eddie Redmayne.
Celia Keyes, played by Juno Temple.
Hector, played by David Tennant.
Glorious 39 is a 2009 British war thriller film written and directed by Stephen Poliakoff, starring Romola Garai, Bill Nighy,
Julie Christie, Jeremy Northam, Christopher Lee, David Tennant, Jenny Agutter, Eddie Redmayne and Charlie Cox.
The film was released on 20 November 2009.
On the eve of the Second World War, as the formidable Keyes family tries to uphold its traditional way of life, daughter
Anne sees her life dramatically unravel when she stumbles upon secret recordings of the appeasement movement.
The film explores themes of adoption, radio, boys' choir, foreign worker, 1930s.
The tone is emotional and intense.